<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- Titles -->
    <string name="settings_title">Settings</string>
    <string name="info_about_app_title">App\nInformation</string>
    <string name="list_of_students_title">List of students\nfor group %s</string>
    <!-- Content -->
    <!--    Settings -->
    <string name="theme_label">Theme:</string>
    <string name="select_text_color_on_orange">Select text color on orange background:</string>
    <string name="some_help_information">Some explanations:
        \n
        \n • About \"Select color on orange background\": When choosing the orange theme or when there
        are laboratory classes in the schedule, I had a question:\"Which color would be better here?
        Black or white?\". So I decided to leave the choice to you.
        \n
        \n • About languages: Since the API does not provide the ability to receive data in different
        languages in a convenient format, there will be some problems and limitations in translation.
        But here\'s the main thing that can be said about languages:
        \n - The application interface is fully translated wherever possible;
        \n - The data received from the API is translated only into Ukrainian and English, but usually,
        in Ukrainian, they will be in a shortened format, and in English - in full. If you choose Russian,
        the API data will be in Ukrainian.
        \n
        \n • About \'Weekday text type in the schedule\': When you open the schedule page, for
        convenience, the day of the week is displayed below the date. And you have the option to choose
        whether it will be \'Thursday\' or \'Thu\'.
        \n
        \n • About \'Lesson type text type\': When you open the schedule page, the type of lesson is displayed
        at the top right. And you can choose how it will be displayed.
        \nExamples: Lecture lesson, Lecture, Lec. Or Laboratory lesson, Laboratory, Lab.
        \n
        \n • About \'Date format\': When you want to choose your own day of the week, the date format will depend
        on this setting. Also, when you are on the schedule page, it will be displayed in this format.
    </string>
    <!--    Info about app -->
    <string name="info_about_app_content">
        <![CDATA[<h1>General Information:</h1>]]>
        From the very beginning, this app was created as a faster and more convenient way to find out
        the schedule, avoiding the use of bots in messengers and the website. But over time, I decided
        to add more functionality, although it still performs its main task excellently.
        <![CDATA[<h1>About the Developers:</h1>]]>
        The app itself was created by a student of the State Tax University, KB-23-1 group
        (at least, at the time of creating the app, I was in this group), Kovalskyi Andrii
        Oleksandrovych (born in 2004). But this app wouldn\'t look like it does now without
        the help of a student from the same university and the group, Hnylosyra Oleksandr Sergiyovych
        (born in 2003). He helped with the overall look of the app.
        <![CDATA[<h1>Agreement Terms:</h1>]]>
        First of all, I want to say that the app does not store any data that can be used against
        you. It only stores the following data: your group identifier and its name,
        your faculty identifier, your course, the time of the last data check, saved
        settings.
        <![CDATA[<br/>]]>
        This means that you automatically agree to have this data saved and used
        for more convenient use of the app. If you disagree, the only thing you can do
        is delete the app and not use it.
        <![CDATA[<br/>]]>
        Also, you agree that the app will send information to the developer about what
        you opened the app and what you used it for. This is necessary for analyzing what may need
        to be changed or removed in the app.
        <![CDATA[<h1>What Can the App Do?</h1>]]>
        The app can do the following:
        - show you today\'s schedule using only 2 clicks, one of which is opening the app;
        <![CDATA[<br/>]]>
        - choose and change your group;
        <![CDATA[<br/>]]>
        - see the bell schedule;
        <![CDATA[<br/>]]>
        - choose settings to your liking.
        <![CDATA[<br/>]]>
        Most likely, this functionality will remain and will not change.
        <![CDATA[<h1>Contact Information:</h1>]]>
        You can find me on Telegram (+380731029662, username - \@Dublongold), Viber
        (+380731029662). You can also write to the email dublon123gold@gmail.com.
        <![CDATA[<br/>]]>
        It is preferable to use them only in case of any malfunctions in the app or if you have
        suggestions for its improvement.
    </string>
    <!-- Button -->
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="look_again">Look Again</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <!-- Other -->
    <string name="white">White</string>
    <string name="black">Black</string>
    <string name="select_language">Language:</string>
    <string name="select_weekday_text_size">Weekday text type in the schedule:</string>
    <string name="select_lesson_type_text_type">Lesson type text type:</string>
    <string name="select_date_format">Date format:</string>
    <string name="question">\?</string>
    <string name="are_you_sure">Are you sure?</string>
    <string name="unsaved_changes">
        It seems you have unsaved changes. Do you want to save them, or do you want to look again?
    </string>
    <string name="bell_schedule_item_start_time">Start: %s</string>
    <string name="bell_schedule_item_end_time">End: %s</string>
    <string name="bell_schedule_item_break">Break: %d min.</string>
    <string name="translate">Translating…</string>
</resources>
