<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- Titles -->
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="want_change_group_title">Change Group</string>
    <string name="data_confirmation_title">Data Confirmation</string>
    <string name="structure_title">Select Structure</string>
    <string name="faculty_title">Select Faculty</string>
    <string name="course_title">Select Course</string>
    <string name="group_title">Select Group</string>
    <!-- Labels -->
    <string name="structure_label">Structure:</string>
    <string name="faculty_label">Faculty:</string>
    <string name="course_label">Course:</string>
    <string name="group_label">Group:</string>
    <!-- Contents -->
    <string name="structure_text">Let\'s start with selecting the structure. I believe your structure is likely
        the State Tax University. But wait for the data to load,
        check if it\'s indeed the State Tax University (or just STU), and then press the \"Next\" button.
    </string>
    <string name="faculty_text">Great! You\'ve chosen the structure <![CDATA[<b>%s</b>]]>.
        <![CDATA[<br>]]>Now, after the data is loaded, select your faculty. For example, if you are studying
        in the \"Computer Science\" specialty, your faculty is
        \"Finance and Digital Technologies.\" But due to the peculiarities of the university\'s API, it may
        be shortened to \"F-T Finance and DT.\" So don\'t be alarmed by the simple lettering, just compare
        the faculties in the list with yours and choose the correct one.
        <![CDATA[<br>]]>After successfully selecting your faculty, press the \"Next\" button.
    </string>
    <string name="course_text">Great! You\'ve chosen the structure <![CDATA[<b>%s</b>]]> and the faculty
        <![CDATA[<b>%s</b>]]>.
        <![CDATA[<br>]]>Now you need to choose the course you are studying. Wait for the data to load,
        choose your course, and press the \"Next\" button.
    </string>
    <string name="group_text">Great! We\'re almost done. You\'ve chosen the structure
        <![CDATA[<b>%s</b>]]>, faculty <![CDATA[<b>%s</b>]]>, and course <![CDATA[<b>%s</b>]]>.
        <![CDATA[<br>]]>Now you need to choose your group. As in the previous steps, wait for the data to finish
        loading, then choose your group. After that, press the \"Next\" button
        and check if everything is correctly specified.
    </string>
    <string name="welcome_text">This app was created so that students of the State
        Tax University could find the schedule for their group in just 1-3 clicks without any authorization.
        \nBut since there are many groups, the college\'s API does not allow
        to immediately select the correct group, and you have just launched this app for the first time, so we will step by step
        narrow down the number of groups and then choose your group.
        \n
        \nThe steps will be as follows:
        \n- specifying your structure;
        \n- specifying your faculty;
        \n- specifying your course;
        \n- selecting your group;
        \n- confirming the selected data.
        \n
        \nIf you\'re ready, press the \"Next\" button and let\'s get started!
    </string>
    <string name="want_change_group_text">If you want to change the group, you need to go through all
        the same steps as in the welcome message. Let me remind you of them:
        \n
        \n- specifying your structure;
        \n- specifying your faculty;
        \n- specifying your course;
        \n- selecting your group;
        \n- confirming the selected data.
        \n
        \nIf you\'re ready, press the \"Next\" button and let\'s get started, or if you\'ve changed your mind,
        press the \"Cancel\" button.
    </string>
    <string name="data_confirmation_text">Congratulations! You\'ve provided all the necessary information and selected your group:
        <![CDATA[<b>%s</b>]]>.
        <![CDATA[<br>]]>
        <![CDATA[<br>]]>If everything is correct, press the \"Confirm\" button and you will be taken to the page with
        the schedule selection for your group. If necessary, you can change
        your group in the future.
        <![CDATA[<br>]]>
        <![CDATA[<br>]]>But if any data does not match, press the \"Back\" button and change what was
        incorrectly specified.
    </string>
    <string name="data_changed_text">Of course, you wanted to see the schedule, but it turns out that on
        the server the data has changed, and your group (or just its identifier) now differs from
        what is saved on your device.
        \n
        \nSo you need to go through the same steps again that you went through in the welcome message. Let me
        remind you of them:
        \n
        \n- specifying your structure;
        \n- specifying your faculty;
        \n- specifying your course;
        \n- selecting your group;
        \n- confirming the selected data.
        \n
        \nIf you\'re ready, press the \"Next\" button and let\'s get started!
    </string>
    <!-- Buttons -->
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
</resources>